<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Founder App</string>
    <string name="elon_musk">Elon musk</string>
    <string name="elon_musk_desc" translatable="false">Tesla is one of the world\'s most valuable
        in terms of market capitalization. In October 2021, Tesla temporarily became a trillion-dollar
        company, the seventh U.S. company to do so. In 2023, the company led the battery electric vehicle
        market, with 19.9% share. Also in 2023, the company was ranked 69th in the Forbes Global 2000.
        As of March 2024, it is the world\'s most valuable automaker. Tesla has been the subject of
        lawsuits, government scrutiny, and journalistic criticism, stemming from allegations of multiple
        cases of whistleblower retaliation, worker rights violations such as sexual harassment and
        anti-union activities, safety defects leading to dozens of recalls, the lack of a public
        relations department, and controversial statements from Musk including overpromising
        on the company\'s driving assist technology and product release timelines.</string>
    <string name="elon_musk_company">Tesla</string>
    <string name="bill_gates">Bill Gates</string>
    <string name="bill_gates_desc">Microsoft was founded by Bill Gates and Paul Allen on April 4, 1975,
        to develop and sell BASIC interpreters for the Altair 8800. It rose to dominate the personal
        computer operating system market with MS-DOS in the mid-1980s, followed by Windows.
        The company\'s 1986 initial public offering (IPO) and subsequent rise in its share price created
        three billionaires and an estimated 12,000 millionaires among Microsoft employees. Since the 1990s,
        it has increasingly diversified from the operating system market and has made several corporate
        acquisitions, the largest being the acquisition of Activision Blizzard for $68.7 billion in October
        2023, followed by its acquisition of LinkedIn for $26.2 billion in December 2016,Nuance Communications
        for $16 billion in March 2022, and Skype Technologies for $8.5 billion in May 2011.</string>
    <string name="bill_gates_company">Microsoft</string>
    <string name="zomato">Zomato</string>
    <string name="zomato_founder">Deepinder Goyal</string>
    <string name="zomato_desc">Zomato is an Indian multinational restaurant aggregator and food delivery
        company. It was founded by Deepinder Goyal and Pankaj Chaddah in 2008.Zomato provides information,
        menus and user-reviews of restaurants as well as food delivery options from partner restaurants
        in more than 1,000 Indian cities and towns, as of 2022–23.Zomato rivals Swiggy in food delivery
        and hyperlocal space.Zomato has earned a Guinness world record for holding the world\'s largest first aid lesson,
        by training 4,300 delivery partners in total, at the single event on June 12th.</string>
    <string name="swiggy">Swiggy</string>
    <string name="swiggy_founder">Sriharsha Majety </string>
    <string name="swiggy_desc">Swiggy is an Indian online food ordering and delivery company. Founded in
        2014, Swiggy is headquartered in Bangalore and operates in more than 580 Indian cities,
        as of July 2023. Besides food delivery, the platform also provides quick commerce services
        under the name Swiggy Instamart, and same-day package deliveries with Swiggy Genie.
        It rivals homegrown startup Zomato in food delivery and hyperlocal marketplace.</string>
    <string name="infosys">Infosys</string>
    <string name="infosys_founder">N.R.Narayana Murthy</string>
    <string name="infosys_desc">Infosys Limited is an Indian multinational technology company that 
        offers business consulting, information technology, and outsourcing services. Founded in Pune,
        the company is headquartered in Bangalore.On 24 August 2021, Infosys became the fourth 
        Indian company to achieve a market capitalization of US$100 billion. It is recognized as one 
        of the leading Big Tech (India) companies.As of 31 March 2024, Infosys is the second-largest
        Indian IT company by revenue and the third-largest Indian company by market capitalization.</string>
    <string name="facebook">Facebook</string>
    <string name="facebook_founder">Mark Elliot Zuckerberg</string>
    <string name="facebook_description">Facebook is a social media and social networking service owned by
        American technology conglomerate Meta. Created in 2004 by Mark Zuckerberg with four other Harvard
        College students and roommates Eduardo Saverin, Andrew McCollum, Dustin Moskovitz, and Chris
        Hughes, its name derives from the face book directories often given to American university
        students. Membership was initially limited to Harvard students, gradually expanding to other North
        American universities. Since 2006, Facebook allows everyone to register from 13 years old, except
        in the case of a handful of nations, where the age limit is 14 years.[6] As of December 2022,
        Facebook claimed almost 3 billion monthly active users.[7] As of October 2023, Facebook ranked
        as the third-most-visited website in the world, with 22.56% of its traffic coming from the
        United States.[8][9] It was the most downloaded mobile app of the 2010s.Facebook can be accessed
        from devices with Internet connectivity, such as personal computers, tablets and smartphones.
        After registering, users can create a profile revealing personal information about themselves.
        They can post text, photos and multimedia which are shared with any other users who have agreed
        to be their friend or, with different privacy settings, publicly. Users can also communicate
        directly with each other with Messenger, join common-interest groups, and receive notifications
        on the activities of their Facebook friends and the pages they follow.</string>
    <string name="tcs">TCS</string>
    <string name="tcs_founder">Faqir Chand Kohli</string>
    <string name="tcs_description">Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) is an Indian multinational technology
        company specializing in information technology services and consulting. Headquartered in Mumbai,
        it is a part of the Tata Group and operates in 150 locations across 46 countries. It is the
        second-largest Indian company by market capitalization.As of 2024, TCS is ranked seventh on the
        Fortune India 500 list.In September 2021, TCS recorded a market capitalization of US$200
        billion, making it the first Indian IT company to achieve this valuation. In 2012,
        it was the world\'s second-largest user of U.S. H-1B visas.In 2024, parent company Tata Sons
        owned 71.74% of TCS, and close to 80% of Tata Sons dividend income came from TCS.</string>
    <string name="wipro">Wipro</string>
    <string name="wipro_founder">Azim Hashim Premji </string>
    <string name="wipro_description">Wipro limited is an Indian multinational technology company
        that provides information technology, consulting and business process services.
        It is one of the six leading Indian Big Tech companies. Wipro\'s capabilities range across
        cloud computing, computer security, digital transformation, artificial intelligence, robotics,
        data analytics, and other technologies, servicing customers in 167 countries.</string>


</resources>